RESUME

ADITYA SANA

Mobile: +91-7780303335 Email: adityasana0234@gmail.com

CAREER OBJECTIVE

A self-motivated and resourceful Lighting Application Engineer / Electrical Engineer with having overall experience of +05 Years providing a strong reputation for accuracy and efficiency.

EXPERIENCE SUMMARY

S. No	Name of the Employer	Work Period	Experience	Designation
01	Uber Project Lighting Pvt Ltd, Hyderabad.	Jan 2021	Current	Lighting Application Engineer / Technical Project Engineer
02	L&T Technologies Services	May 2019 – Oct 2020	1 Year 7 Months	Lighting Application Engineer
03	K&J Projects Pvt.Ltd	Sep 2016 – May 2019	2 Years 8 Months	Jr. Electrical Engineer
04	Mars Turbo India Pvt.Ltd	July 2015- Aug 2016	1 year 2 Months	Electrical Site Engineer

ROLES AND RESPONSIBILITIES:

Uber Project Lighting Pvt Ltd., Hyderabad | Lighting Application Engineer / Technical Project Engineer | Currently Working.

- Participating in Technical and Commercial Tenders (Bids) as per RFP Documents.
- Designing and making project bill of quantities sheets and giving the technical support for the same.
- Developing project objectives by reviewing project proposals and plans and conferring with management.
- Determining project specifications by studying product design, customer requirements, and performance standards.
- Controls project plan by reviewing design, specifications, and plan, scheduling changes, and recommending actions.
- Maintains project schedule by monitoring project progress, coordinating activities, and resolving problems.
- Formulating project parameters and assigning responsibilities to the most capable employees and monitoring the project team.
- Coordinate's materials and assists in the logistics, its shipment and receipt at construction site.
- Attends the Weekly Progress Meetings (Internal as well as with Client) and assist in preparation of Minutes of Meetings.
- Assists in preparation and implementation of Project Execution Plan (PEP).
- Monitors work in progress and prepares weekly report of the status of each assignment.
- Ensuring all procedures and calculations are submitted to the client for review and approval.
- Developing project objectives by reviewing project proposals and plans and conferring with management.

- Surveying quantities at site, preparing, and submitting the running account bills.
- Contribution to team effort by accomplishing related results as needed.
- Basically, looking after the project from the initial stage (Participating in Bids, Product selection, approvals) to final Handover stage.

DETAILED SUMMARY OF WORK EXPERIENCE

- 1). Gar Corporation Private Limited, Tower 8&9, Hyderabad. (Current Running Project-1)
- 2). PayPal India private Limited, Chennai_2020-21. (Current Running Project-2)
- 3). Amazon Development Centre (I) Pvt Ltd, SEZ Main Campus, Nannakramguda, Hyderabad_2019-21. (Current Running Project-3)

L&T Technology Services., Gujarat | Lighting Application Engineer | May 2019 - Oct 2020.

- Provides Lighting design of Architectural, Commercial & Residential layouts using Dialux Software.
- Prepares Lighting Presentation, Lighting layouts and Bill of quantity for the Project designed and
- · presenting the same before the clients,
- Contributing as Application Engineer/ Electrical Lighting Engineer, and working towards managing all
 the RFAs for control layouts Showcasing proven excellence in preparing Lighting Control Layouts, Bill
 of Materials and Lighting Control Submittals
- Ensuring the designs, studies, surveys and investigations are appropriate and meet the expected levels of technical excellence Monitoring performance of the lighting asset and identifying areas of weakness.
- Preparing the technical specifications and daily work reports; submitting the same to the management
- Coordinating with the staff in implementing strategies to increase productivity and reduce cost of power.
- Playing an active role in reviewing lighting plans and blueprints including costs and budget
- Having expert knowledge of different brands of Lighting Controls like Watt stopper, nLight, Sensor
- Switch, LC&D panels, FRESCO, Blue Box, Lutron, Leviton and so on
- Providing a feasible lighting control solution complying requirements per regional Codes and Client
- using Visual Control Software.
- Preparation of Budgetary Offer, BOM and construction packages
- Showcasing proven excellence in preparing Lighting Control Layouts, Bill of Materials and Lighting
- Control Submittals
- Executed 200+ Order (projects) during tenure with 100% Quality and timely submission.
- Having good Knowledge of Lighting, Luminaries, and lamps.
- Maintaining Lesson Learn and Root Cause Analysis on weekly basis.

DETAILED SUMMARY OF WORK EXPERIENCE:

- 1) AMAZON COLORADO SPRINGS 2
- 2) CHIPOTTLE MEXICAN GRILL STORE
- 3) COMCAST INVERNESS 3RD FLOOR.
- 4) NATIONAL JEWISH-COH-CORE SHELL.
- 5) NCSD SCHELLENBERG CAMPUS IMPROVEMENTS.
- 6) SLADE ELEMENTARY
- 7) CANDLEWOOD SUITES WESTGATE @ POWERS
- 8) CSU CENTER FOR FOOD AND AGRICULTURE
- 9) CHIPOTTLE MEXICAN GRILL STORE @ TEMPLE TERRACE
- 10) MICRON BUILDING 32

K&J Projects Pvt.Ltd., Hyderabad | Junior Electrical Engineer | Sept 2016 – May 2019.

- Good understanding of MEP AutoCAD drawings, planning of projects, execution, client bill making, contractor bills making, Boq quantity checking as per drawing.
- Client drawings modifications and as built preparing in AutoCAD as per project execution.

- Project reporting, site co-ordination, client meeting presentation and team supervision.
- Client bill and subcontractor bills making as per site execution.
- To manage subcontractor, vendor, and manpower as per site condition for work.
- Checking of BOQ quantity as per client drawing, cost estimation and materials indent.
- Preparing all work checklists, weekly and monthly reports.
- Checking of conducting in conceal slabs, proper wiring through conduits, switch boards, light fittings, db dressing, and prepare checklists and as built drawings.
- Adept at analyze problems and rapidly finding solutions.

SOFTWARE/ TOOL CAPABILITY: -

AutoCAD, Revit from Autodesk, Visual Controls & Dialux 4.12

MEP SKILLS

Project Coordination, Project Management, Site, Project Execution, Mechanical, Financial Flow Control, Design, Execution and Commissioning.

EDUCATION QUALIFICATIONS

- 2009 2013 | Bachelor of Engineering in Electrical from Mithra Institute of Technology, Srikakulam, A.P with an aggregate of 62%.
- 2007 2009 | Intermediate MPC at Sri Chaitanya Jr. College, Visakhapatnam, A.P with an aggregate of 80%.
- 2009 | SCC at Sri Prakash Vidyalayam High School, Visakhapatnam, A.P with an aggregate of 65%.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Name : Sana Aditya

Father's Name : Sana lava Kumar

Date of Birth : 29-Aug-1992

Gender : Male

Marital Status : Single

Nationality : Indian

Languages Known : English, Telugu, Hindi

Permanent Address : Door No-25-248, Sanjiv Gandhi Colony, Visakhapatnam, Andhra Pradesh.

Phone No. : +91-7780303335

Gmail : adityasana0234@gmail.com

DECLARATION

I hereby declare that the information given herewith is true to my knowledge and I will be responsible for any discrepancy.

Place: Hyderabad Yours truly

Sana Aditya